# ANKUR BHARGAVA

#### Mumbai

Phone: (91) 9820965953 email: ankurbhargava0511@gmail.com

# Work Experience (12+yr)

Associate/AVP- J.P. Morgan (2013 → Now)

Project Executions for Credit Derivatives Trade Processing. Manage a suite of applications which are mission critical for Trade booking, Post trade workflow, Risk and PL, Reconciliations and Reference Data Services, etc.

• Tech Lead-Polaris Software Lab Ltd (2010 → 2013)

Working on JPMorgan Project. Blotters, Risk/PL, Reconciliations

• Tech Lead -Steria India Pvt. Limited (2010)

Working for AXA- Health Care and insurance

 Programmer Analyst -Cognizant Technology Solution(2009-2010)

Health care system, Hospital Management, PHR

Software Engineer- UST Global (2006-2009)

Health care and insurance, Advance Life income and compensation system. Client -WellPoint.

### Education

B-Tech- 2006 - 77.28% (9th University Merit)

SSC - UP BOARD - 2001 - 76.2%

HSC - UP BOARD - 1999 - 82.83%

Certificates-Oracle Certified Associate

### Profile

I am full stack developer and have worked with varied set of technologies across the span of my career.

I have worked with Credit Derivatives / Securities and health care and have understanding of Front office and Middle Office Functions.

I also have experience in Project Execution, delivery, stakeholder management, task management.

## Expertise

- .Net WPF/Winform
- Python
- SQL Server/Oracle/Sybase
- SSRS/SSIS
- Messaging
- UI Development
- Nunit/XUnit Test
- Micro Service API(Rest)
- JS/React(Basic)
- Credit Derivatives/Securities
- Post/Pre Trade Processing
- Risk/PL
- Health Care /Claim Processing